// English Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What type of punctuation should be at the end of this sentence??",
    answer: "Question mark ?",
    options: [
      "Period",
      "Question mark ?",
      "Exclamation point !",
      "Comma"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which word best shows joy?",
    answer: "amusement",
    options: [
      "slumped",
      "amusement",
      "slouched",
      "confused"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Bianca wants to know how the caterpillars become a butterfly, what will she use?",
    answer: "Encyclopedia",
    options: [
      "Dictionary",
      "Encyclopedia",
      "Thesaurus",
      "Atlas"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The repetition of sounds at the end of words",
    answer: "rhyme",
    options: [
      "metaphor",
      "rhythm",
      "rhyme",
      "simile"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The use of a word, phrase, or line more than once",
    answer: "repetition",
    options: [
      "repetition",
      "alliteration",
      "personification",
      "rhythm"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "What is a narrative?",
  answer: "a story",
  options: [
    "informational article",
    "a story",
    "anything written by an author",
    "most social studies books"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "What is the purpose of a text feature?",
  answer: "to add meaning",
  options: [
    "for entertainment",
    "to add meaning",
    "to confuse the reader",
    "to please your teacher"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "Select the adjectives in the following sentence. 'The road comprised large houses and a tiny shop'.",
  answer: "large, tiny",
  options: [
    "houses, shop",
    "large, tiny",
    "comprised, and",
    "road, large"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Select the adjectives in the following sentence.'The old book had lost its original cover long ago'.",
  answer: "old, original",
  options: [
    "book, cover",
    "old, original",
    "lost, long",
    "The, its"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "Select the adjectives in the following sentence. 'The long transporter delivered the new car today'.",
  answer: "long, new",
  options: [
    "long, new",
    "delivered, today",
    "The, the",
    "transporter, car"
  ]
},

];
